Hello?
Do something.
If not, you'll get dragged into this.
We all know that fake news is everywhere.
This isn't just an ordinary issue.
This is a crime.
So whoever you are
who's trying to mess with us,
no matter where you are,
I'll find you.
Hi, this is Billy speaking.
Oh my gosh, Ms. Billy!
Is that really you?
[BILLY] Abi, it's you.
[ABI] Congratulations again!
You're amazing, idol!
It's so soft!
Must be nice.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Wow. I didn't know you had a fan.
[SCOFFS] Don't be silly.
I just feel sorry for Abi.
Auntie Pres, listen to this.
She said her father
and sister abandoned her.
She was left all alone
to take care of her mother.
I told her
that maybe she needs to take a break.
Go on vacation.
She could get a caregiver for her mom.
Correct. Why doesn't she do that?
I don't think she can afford to.
I think their business
is struggling or something.
[BILLY] I want to help her, Auntie Pres.
I feel a sense of…
It's not pity.
Maybe potential?
Connection?
[GASPS]
Wait a minute.
[GUSHES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Listen to me, Benilda.
You don't have to help
every woman in need.
Don't you have
enough problems of your own to fix?
Yes, I agree. Okay.
Can we eat already?
I'm hungry.
Did you hear that? That's a big problem.
[BILLY] You got that right, Auntie Pres.
- He calls the shots. Let's go.
- [JORDAN] Come on.
Come on, let's go.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Just need a pair of shoes.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SPRITZING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BILLY] Have you seen
my red shoes, Auntie?
The pair I wore
to the LoveList anniversary party.
No.
Goodness, Billy.
You're becoming so forgetful.
First, you lost your keys.
Now, it's your shoes.
Maybe you left them in the car.
You leave spares in your car, right?
You switch to rubber shoes
when your feet get sore.
No, Auntie.
I remember that night,
I got out of the car holding my shoes.
Then where are they?
[WOMAN 1] Wow! How beautiful!
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMAN 2] Looking good, miss!
[MAN] Wow!
[WOMAN 2] Did you see her?
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GASPS]
[MALE OFFICER]
Carlos Toledo, you're free to go.
Your bail has been posted.
Huh?
[LOCK CLANKING]
[GRUNTS]
[DOOR HANDLE CRANKS]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
It's all good now, ma'am. I've changed it.
Perfect! Thank you, mister.
Here.
Oh, wait.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Thanks too.
Paranoid much?
Better safe than sorry, Auntie.
I can't find my old key.
- Someone might break in.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
At least we're safe.
[CHUCKLES]
- Something interesting?
- Huh?
It's your app.
It's really something.
I keep receiving notifications. Uh, I…
I accepted Brandon's request.
Well, that's what happens when
you click "Accept."
So how do you find Brandon?
- Hmm?
- How do you find him?
Well, he's a volunteer at the orphanage,
and he seems active
in feeding programs for children.
Plus, he's handsome, so that's a bonus.
You're perfect for each other.
He also likes to cook.
You forgot to log out.
- [GASPS] Oh, you!
- [BILLY CHUCKLES]
- [BILLY] Busted!
- You're so nosy.
- Hurry up and finish eating.
- [PHONE RINGING]
The bus will be here soon.
Hello?
Dude, Caloy just posted bail.
What?
Come on. I'm on my way.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CALOY HUFFS]
- Hey, man.
- Oh.
You two again?
Are you giving me a ride home?
Who bailed you out?
Was it your boss?
How many times do I have to tell you both?
I don't even know who my boss is!
Someone just left the money
outside my house.
Are we done here?
Caloy, just tell us the truth.
You haven't learned your lesson, have you?
Are you threatening us?
We won't stop
until we send you back to jail.
And when that happens,
I'll make sure that you rot in there.
You bastard!
You're also annoying.
I could stab you, you know?
- Don't you dare!
- Jordan.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're lucky I just got released.
Otherwise, I would've let you two have it.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Her face is flawless, and she's so pretty.
She has soft hands too.
She has all these nice clothes,
makeup, and shoes.
Plus, she smells good.
She smells really good!
You're getting envious again.
You're so jealous of her.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's not like that, Ma.
You see, she also has a nice car.
She has nice stuff,
and her business is doing good.
And it seems…
she has a happy family.
That made me wonder.
Did she have a hard time in life?
But I don't think so.
She's a lucky woman. She's so lucky.
She's very lucky.
Call your sister. Let's eat.
Ma, why are there only three plates?
I told you to call your sister.
Did you know she got promoted?
Your sister is really amazing.
She's so smart.
Oh come on, Ma.
I was just asking why
there were only three plates,
and you keep blabbing about Abi.
So why are there only three plates?
Is Papa not coming home?
Isn't he joining us?
You are so dumb, aren't you?
You're stupid!
You really take after your father.
You're both useless!
So, what?
Are you going to take his side, huh?
Then get out of here and go with him!
You deserve each other anyway!
[SCREAMING]
[PLATES SHATTER]
- [MARIELA SCREAMING]
- [PLATES SHATTER]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What happened?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[WIND WHOOSHING]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[ABIGAIL PANTING]
Ma! Ma!
[SCREAMING, PANTING]
Ma!
[ABIGAIL COUGHS]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ABIGAIL BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [THUD]
- [ABIGAIL WHIMPERS]
Ma!
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [FIRE CRACKLING]
- [WOOD THUDS]
- [ABIGAIL GASPS]
[ABIGAIL PANTING]
Ma! Ma!
Ma.
[ABIGAIL GRUNTS]
- Oh my God!
- Help!
Ma! Ma!
- Take her.
- Ma.
- Help her.
- Help! Ma.
Ma, wake up! Ma!
Ma.
[LABORED BREATHING]
- Abigail.
- [OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Abigail! Abigail!
- [ABIGAIL BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Abigail.
Abigail.
Abigail!
[MUSIC FADING]
But don't worry, Ma.
Luck is finally on our side.
It's close.
I can feel it.
It's coming.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You're still seriously hoping
things will get better?!
You really are stupid,
just like your father.
You're so naïve,
to think that luck will find us.
There's no hope for us! This is it!
Look at me! Just look at me!
Your nose has longer hair than my head.
[LAUGHS]
Right?
[LAUGHS] Let me see your armpit.
Let me see.
[LAUGHS]
You have a lot of hair.
[LAUGHTER]
They're really long. I swear.
- [STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [MARIELA LAUGHING]
Toledo was granted bail on the
grounds of self-defense.
What?
Attorney, we both know that's not true.
What can we do to send him back to jail?
Well, we can file a motion to revoke bail
or a motion for reconsideration.
- But it won't be easy, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
We need to present a compelling reason,
such as new evidence
or a violation of bail conditions.
For now, just make sure
you don't do anything illegal
that Toledo might use against you.
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Boss, this place feels sketchy.
You bet. Our boss got stabbed here.
This seems like a bad decision.
Let's go, boss.
That jerk threatened Billy. Come on.
That's him! There he is!
What's your plan?
- Let's beat him up.
- Hey, what are you saying?
We agreed that we'd resolve this
through peaceful dialogue.
Seriously, boss?
I love you, but my love has limits.
- Come on, let's beat him up.
- No, no, no. Not yet.
Let's see where he goes.
I'm scared.
If I had beaten him up,
he wouldn't have reached the door.
- He'd all be black and blue.
- Shh.
Peaceful dialogue? Yeah, right.
You have to be extra careful, Billy.
How did that Caloy
even get released from jail?
- He's got a strong backer.
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you for your concern.
Here. It wards off evil spirits.
- You need that.
- Oh my God, guys! Look!
My feature on LoveLine
got a million views in just 12 hours.
Wow! Nice, twinny Val!
How many views did you get?
I love your feature, twinny Val!
Hopefully, we can do a collab next time
and make content
on Switch Lives with Blaire.
It will be easy for you.
Let's go!
You're a content creator too?
Here.
- Hmm.
- [BLAIRE] See?
Wow.
Our numbers are up. Right, Toni?
Oh, yes.
Our engagement is up by 48%.
Our ad clicks also doubled.
Billy, I'm sorry that
I had doubts about this before.
I mean, it's so risky to take a gamble
on LoveLine without any investors.
It was risky. Yes.
But growth doesn't come
from playing safe, right?
Thank you all for taking the leap with me.
That's what makes this team different.
So congratulations, and good job, girls.
[CLAPPING, CHEERING]
This calls for a group hug! Yes.
- I want to join.
- Me too.
- Fine. I'll join too.
- Group hug!
- This is nice.
- Yeah.
Okay.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Robbie, Rain, wake up.
He's leaving. Come on.
- That way.
- Come on.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't make any noise.
How are you?
Are you okay?
You really had to go back there?
Huh?
- [BILLY] Hmm?
- [JORDAN] Who told you?
We've got lots of customers.
They come at this hour.
Well?
Dude, before you get mad,
we saw him talking to someone
inside a cab.
We don't know who it was,
but that person handed him an envelope.
So it's not true that Caloy
doesn't know who it is.
Did you get the license plate?
Yes, ma'am, but the operator won't tell us
where the passenger was dropped off.
We have to secure a court order first.
[RAIN] You know, I'm scared of Caloy.
He looks like someone who can kill.
Exactly. So promise me
you won't go back there, dude.
It's dangerous.
Hey.
Come on, dude. You have to promise me.
- Boss, make a promise.
- [BILLY] But thank you.
Thank you.
[RAIN] Uh, Ma'am Billy…
Where was Valerie around 7:00 p.m.?
Seven? I'm not sure.
But I know she was already
out of the office.
[ROBBIE] Oh.
Do you think it was Valerie?
[RAIN] Yes. It's--
I have a strong feeling that it was her.
[ROBBIE GROANS] I don't know.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hi there, Ms. Billy Idol.
I'm at your house.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DOORKNOB RATTLING]
- [KEYS JINGLING]
[CHUCKLES] Oops. Wrong key.
- Why won't it open?
- [DOORKNOB RATTLING]
I used this key before.
[DOORKNOB RATTLING]
- [DOORKNOB RATTLING]
- [KEYS JINGLING]
Aah!
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yes, Freddie. We are open to sponsorships.
We can play your ads
while on call waiting.
Yes, we can also put your names
as sponsors on the posters and billboards.
Mall shows?
Two years?
Yes, we can do that as well.
Okay.
I'll let you know. Thank you.
[BRIGHT HOPEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Chief, are we on?
Please tell me we have a deal.
Yes. They'll send us the contract!
We have a deal!
- We have a deal!
[JORDAN] We have a deal, baby! Let's go!
- [APPLAUDING]
- Congratulations!
- Thank you!
- Finally, some good news.
[BILLY] See?
We just need to think positive!
Finally, we're going to make some money!
[BILLY] Wait a minute, Toni.
Let's use the money
for system improvements first.
[BILLY] Let's help each other
out first, okay?
[TONI] Okay.
I wasn't informed that
this was a foundation.
[CHUCKLES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I'd like to ask you something
about your passenger.
I remember what she looked like.
But this is a different story.
Didn't you get stabbed?
That's our best shot right now.
He's our only lead to the woman
who gave him the money.
I went to your office just before,
and someone was there.
Didn't you say you would give me
a tour of your office?
Oliver really is my inspiration.
- [BULLIES] Twig! Twig!
- That's enough!
[BULLIES JEER]
What kind of person
doesn't love their sibling?
By the way, Billy,
I don't like that face of yours!